Guide to the Larry Spruch Papers MC.209
New York University Archives
- Series IV: Professional Materials, 1927-2004; 1950-2002
  - Subseries B: Works by Other Physicists, 1927-2004; 1950-2002
    - Turner, Michael S., 1992 (Box 21, Folder 48)
    - van Horn, Hugh, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 49)
    - van Kampen, N. G., B. R. A. Nijboer, and K. Schram, 1968, 1973, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 50)
    - van Wageningen, R., 1957 (Box 21, Folder 51)
    - Vattay, Gábor, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 52)
    - Ventura, Joseph, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 53)
    - Virtamo, J., 1976 (Box 21, Folder 54)
    - Voller, Michael and Frank Träger, 1986-1988 (Box 21, Folder 55)
    - von Baeyer, Hans Christian, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 56)
    - Wadehra, J. M., 1976 (Box 21, Folder 57)
    - Wadehra, J. M., 1977-1984 (Box 21, Folder 58)
    - Wadehra, J. M., 1981 (Box 21, Folder 59)
    - Wadehra, J. M., undated (Box 21, Folder 60)
    - Wagoner, Robert V., 1967 (Box 21, Folder 61)
    - Weidenmüller, Hans A., 1984-1994 (Box 21, Folder 62)
    - Weikard, Rudi, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 63)
    - Weinberg, Steven, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Weinberg, Steven, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Weinberg, Steven, 1963-1964 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Weinberg, Steven, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Weisskopf, V., 1938-1977 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Weisskopf, V. F., 1969 (Box 22, Box 6)
    - West, Geoffrey B., Frederick M. Cooper, Emil Mottola, and Michael P. Mattis, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Widom, Allan, 1990-1997 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Wilczek, Frank, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Wintgen, Dieter, 1986-1987 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Wintgen, D. and H. Friedrich, undated (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Wiser, Nathan, D. L. Dexter, and Stephen L. Adler, 1955-1963 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Wunner, G. and H. Ruder, 1980-1981 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Wunner, G. and H. Ruder, 1986-1988 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Yablonovitch, E., 1989 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Yakhontov, V. L. and M. Ya Amusia, 1981-1995 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Yakhontov, V. L., 1993-1996 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Zumino, Bruno, 1954-1977 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - zu Putlitz, G., 1996 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Zygelman, Bernard, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Alphabetical reprint files: B, 1950-1990 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Alphabetical reprint files: D, 1951-1965 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Alphabetical reprint files: F, 1949-1977 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Alphabetical reprint files: G, 1943-1993 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Alphabetical reprint files: H, 1955-1980 (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Alphabetical reprint files: K, 1940-1994 (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - Alphabetical reprint files: L, 1944-1996 (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - Alphabetical reprint files: M, 1951-1981 (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - Alphabetical reprint files: N, 1957, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - Alphabetical reprint files: O, 1949-1964, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - Alphabetical reprint files: P, 1956-1984 (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - Alphabetical reprint files: R, 1950-1969, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - Alphabetical reprint files: S, 1957-1998 (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - Alphabetical reprint files: T, 1927, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 34)
    - Alphabetical reprint files: W, 1947-1992 (Box 22, Folder 35)
    - Alphabetical reprint files: Y-Z, 1950, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 36)
    - "Estimates of diagonal elements of Green's function using geometrical methods (infinite)" manuscript, author unknown, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 37)
    - English summaries of articles published in Alexander von Humboldt Foundation magazine, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 38)
    - American Physical Society News, vol. 1 no. 5 (clipping), 1992 (Box 22, Folder 39)
    - Bulletin of the American Physical Society, volume 23, number 6, 1948 (Box 22, Folder 40)
    - American Scientist, volume 88 and 89 (clippings), 2000-2001 (Box 22, Folder 41)
    - Atomic, Molecular, and Plasma Physics books catalogue, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 42)
    - Bulletin of the Atomic Scientists, 1977, 1986-1987 (Box 22, Folder 43)
    - Center for Theoretical Studies bulletin, VI-2, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 44)
    - Comments on Nuclear and Particle Physics volume 21, number 3 (clipping), 1993 (Box 22, Folder 45)
    - General Physics and Physical Review abstracts (clippings), 1987-1996 (Box 22, Folder 46)
    - Institute for Theoretical Physics: The Niels Bohr Institute, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 47)
    - Institut d'Astrophysique Compte rendu d'activité scientifique pour l'année 1968, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 48)
    - Joint Institute for Laboratory Astrophysics reports, 1969-1978 (Box 22, Folder 49)
    - Journal of Mathematical Physics (clippings), 1960-1963 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Lunar Nomenclature IAU Working Group report, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Mosaic, National Science Foundation magazine, 1990-1991 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - New York University Magazine (clipping), 1986 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Physics for Scientists and Engineers Superconductivity Supplement, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Physics News, 1987-1988 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Physics News, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Physical Science Magazine (Japanese), 1987 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Physical Review (clippings), 1946-1965 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Physics Today (clippings), 1973-1986 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Physics Today (clippings), 1979-1987 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Physics Today volume 34 number 11, 1981 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Physics Today volume 40 number 2, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Physics Today (clippings), 1988-1990 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Physics Today (clippings), 1991-1993 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Physics Today (clippings), 1994-1997 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Physics Today (clippings), 1998-1999 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Physics Today (clippings), 2000-2002 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Physics Today (clippings), 2003-2004 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Reports of the DFG (clippings), 1985 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Science (clipping), 1986 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Science and Public Affairs, 1973-1974 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - The Sciences (clipping), 2000 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - U.S. Naval Research Laboratory Annotated Bibliography on Positron Scattering, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - Zeitschrift für Physik A (clippings)3, 1977-1978 (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - Cambridge University Press catalog (clippings), undated (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - Princeton University Press catalog (clippings), undated (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - Articles by various physicists for Larry Spruch website, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - Progress reports on research contracts between NYU and U.S. government agencies, 1956-1973 (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - International Directory of Workers in the Field of Atomic and Molecular Physics, Oak Ridge National Laboratory, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - Articles on atomic scattering processes, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 31)
    - Articles on atoms in strong magnetic fields, 1969, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 32)
    - Articles and citations on the Casimir effect, 1995-2002 (Box 23, Folder 37)
    - Articles on the Casimir effect in Biology, 1994, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 38)
    - Casimir effect "odds and ends", 1994 (Box 23, Folder 39)
    - Articles on Casimir force measurement, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 40)
    - Articles on Casimir forces, 1998-1999 (Box 23, Folder 41)
    - Fragment on the Coase Theorem in Economics, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Articles on cosmology, 1979-1983 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Articles on Coulomb and Polarization potential, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Deduction of 1/r using coupled equations and Green's Functions, 1959 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Articles on dispersion relations, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Articles on the dynamical Casimir effect and three-dimensional oscillating cavities, 1997-2002 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Articles on electron capture, 1927-1976 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Articles on Feynman path integrals, 1969-1972 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Articles on Green's function, undated (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Articles on the interstellar medium, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Articles on low-energy scattering, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Articles on the Low theorem, 1965-1974 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Articles on Modified Effective Range Theory, 1961, 1977, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Articles on muon physics, 1980-1985 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Articles on various nuclear reactions, 1951-1986 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Articles on nucleosynthesis, 1958, 1963, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Articles on perturbation, 1959-1967 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Articles on positron interactions with solid surfaces, 1976-1979 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Articles on pulsars, 1965-1974 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Articles on quantum electrodynamics, 1980-1981 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Articles on radiation and magnetic fields, 1983-1986 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Materials on radiative corrections, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Articles on relativistic charge transfer, 1979, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Articles on sonoluminescence, 1988-1993 (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Articles on supernova cosmology, 1997-1999 (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Notes on supervariational principles, author unknown, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Articles on Thomas-Fermi theory, 1975-1983 (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Articles on threshold phenomena, 1957-1979 (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - Articles on variational principles, 1967-1971 (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - Articles on variational principles, 1974-1976 (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - Various reprints, "Class I", 1969, 1985-1987 (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - Various reprints, "Class III", 1983-1988 (Box 24, Folder 32)
    - Various clippings and articles, 1963, 1993-2002 (Box 24, Folder 33)
    - Articles on various topics, 1950-1954 (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - Articles on various topics, 1975-1991 (Box 24, Folder 35)
    - Articles on various topics, 1986-1993 (Box 24, Folder 36)
    - Photocopied page of a book: "Relation to facilitate the calculation of explicit formulas", undated (Box 24, Folder 37)
  - Subseries C: Conferences, Workshops, and Seminars, 1956-2003
    - Seminars on Scattering, University College, London and Institute of Mathematical Sciences, 1956, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - IBM colloquium, 1958 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - International Conference on Nuclear Forces and the Few-Nucleon Problem, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - International Conference on Nuclear Structure, 1960 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Long Range Forces Colloquium, 1960-1967 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Notes for invited paper given at Mexico City, 1961 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - First Eastern Theoretical Physics Conference, 1962 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Third International Conference on the Physics of Electronic and Atomic Collisions, 1963 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Conference on Low and Medium Energy Nuclear Physics, 1963 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - International Three Body Problem Symposium, 1964 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Conference on Correlations of Particles Emitted in Nuclear Reactions, 1964 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - University of Colorado Summer Institute, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Report on the Ninth Yugoslav Summer Meeting of Physicists, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Symposium on Atomic Interactions and Space Physics; Fourth International Conference on the Physics of Electronic and Atomic Collisions, 1965, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Summer School in Theoretical Physics and Chemistry, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Summer Institute for Theoretical Physics, University of Colorado, Boulder, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Talk on Long-Range Forces, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Leningrad Conference on Atomic Scattering, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - International Conference on the Physics of Electronic and Atomic Collisions, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - International Conference on the Physics of Electronic and Atomic Collisions, 1967, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - International Conference on Atomic Physics, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Arnold Sommerfeld Centennial Memorial Meeting, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Physique Fondamentale et Astrophysique, Colloque du CNRS, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - Varenna Summer School, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Topics in Low Energy Scattering Theory Seminar, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - International Astronomical Union 14th General Assemby, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - International Conference on the Physics of Electronic and Atomic Collisions, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - International Conference on the Physics of Electronic and Atomic Collisions, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - Variational Principles and Three Body Breakup Processes Colloquium, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - Cargèse Summer Institute, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 30)
    - Molecules and Computers Conference, 1971-1972 (Box 25, Folder 31)
    - Travel forms for Colorado, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 32)
    - Graduate student pre-colloquium talk by Sucher, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 33)
    - Storrs talk, 1972-1973 (Box 25, Folder 34)
    - Aspen Center for Physics, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 35)
    - Coral Gables Conferences on Fundamental Interactions, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 36)
    - Gordon Research Conferences on Atomic Physics, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 37)
    - University of Pennsylvania Physics and Society Seminar, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 38)
    - Fifth Annual Meeting of the Division of Electron and Atomic Physics, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 39)
    - Aspen Center for Physics, 1973-1983 (Box 25, Folder 40)
    - International Symposium on Electron and Photon Interactions with Waves; Fourth International Conference on Atomic Physics, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 41)
    - Office of Naval Research meeting in Arlington, VA, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 42)
    - Aspen Center for Physics, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 43)
    - International Symposium on "Electron and Photon Interactions with Atoms", 1974 (Box 25, Folder 44)
    - Graduate student seminar on Variational Principles, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 45)
    - Aspen Center for Physics, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 46)
    - Atoms in Intense Magnetic Fields Colloquium, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 47)
    - Seventh International Conference on Few Body Problems in Nuclear and Particle Physics, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 48)
    - James Franck Institute Seminars, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 49)
    - Aspen Center for Physics, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 50)
    - Aspen Center for Physics and various other conferences, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 51)
    - Tenth International Conference on the Physics of Electronic and Atomic Collisions, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 52)
    - Gordon Research Conferences on Atomic Physics, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 53)
    - Center for Astrophysics telephone directory, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 54)
    - Conference on Atomic Scattering Theory: Mathematical and Computational Aspects, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 55)
    - International Conference on the Physics of Electronic and Atomic Collisions, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 56)
    - George J. Schulz Memorial Lecture and Symposium, 1977, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 57)
    - Sixth International Conference on Atomic Physics, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 58)
    - American Physical Society Division of Electron and Atomic Physics Annual Meeting, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 59)
    - Conference on the Mathematical and Computational Aspects of Atomic Scattering Theory, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 60)
    - Gordon Research Conferences, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 61)
    - Los Alamos National Laboratory, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 62)
    - Soviet Union talk, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 63)
    - Charge Transfer talk given at Yale and Los Alamos, 1978-1979 (Box 25, Folder 64)
    - Brandt Conference, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 65)
    - Presentation of work by Spruch and Leonard Rosenberg, Kyoto: Variational Principle for Scattering Length of the Target Wave Function Imprecisely known, 1977-1979 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Transparencies for Kyoto presentation by Larry Spruch and Leonard Rosenberg, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - International Conference on the Physics of Electronic and Atomic Collisions, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Seminar at Rice University and Texas A & M, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Gordon Research Conferences on Atomic Physics, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Aspen Center for Physics, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - American Physical Society meeting, Washington, D.C., 1979-1980 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Seventh International Conference on Atomic Physics, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Thomas-Fermi Colloquium, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Colloquium on Variational Principles, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Transparencies for University of Mexico talk, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Seminario "Manuel Sandoval Vallarta", 1981 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Gordon Conference on Atomic Physics, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Instituto de Fisica, Universidad Nacional Autónoma de México, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Long range potentials talk: NYU and DEAP, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Aspen Center for Physics, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Eastern Theoretical Physics Conference, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Eighth International Conference on Atomic Physics, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - University of Southern California colloquium and John S. Blair Symposium, University of Washington, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Lewes Center for Physics, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Symposium on Collisions in Strong Fields and Thirteenth International Conference on the Physics of Electronic and Atomic Collisions, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Charge Transfer in Asymptotia Colloquium, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Transparencies for talk on "Photoexcitation and photoejection of electrons image-bound to a wall," given by Larry Spruch and Robin Shakeshaft at DEAP American Physical Society meeting, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - Talk on Thomas-Fermi theory, given at the University of Colorado, Boulder, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - Aspen Center for Physics, 1984-1990 (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - Conference invitations, 1986-1999 (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - Alexander von Humboldt Foundation U.S. Humboldt Award Symposium, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - Semiclassical Descriptions of Atomic and Nuclear Collisions Symposium, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 28)
    - Transparencies for conference talks on "Radioactive decay and the age of the galaxy" and "Atomic effects of beta decay on Astro- and Elementary Particle Physics", 1987-1988 (Box 26, Folder 29)
    - Romania SCOFEI, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 30)
    - Conference in Honor of Alexander Dalgarno's Sixtieth Birthday on Atomic and Molecular Processes, with Applications to Aeronomy and Astrophysics, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 31)
    - Workshop on Long Range Forces in Few Body Systems, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 32)
    - Dana Palmer House, Harvard, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 33)
    - Dalitz Conference, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 34)
    - Aspen Center for Physics, 1991-1996 (Box 26, Folder 35)
    - Casimir Potentials colloquium, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 36)
    - University of Minnesota colloquium, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 37)
    - Photocopies of transparencies used in presentation on article in Science, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 38)
    - Los Alamos Summer School, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 39)
    - NYU Physics department Spring Colloquium, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 40)
    - Symposium in Honor of Larry Spruch's Seventieth Birthday, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 41)
    - American Physical Society Panel on Public Affairs (POPA), 1993-1996 (Box 26, Folder 42)
    - Symposium and breakfast in Larry Spruch's honor, 1993, 2002-2003 (Box 26, Folder 43)
    - Transparencies from "Casimir Effects from a Relatively Elementary Viewpoint" talk, 1994-1997 (Box 26, Folder 44)
    - Fourteenth International Conference on Atomic Physics, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 45)
    - Tenth Biennial Association of the Members of the Institute for Advanced Study (AMIAS) Conference, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 46)
    - Max-Planck-Institute for Nuclear Physics, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 47)
    - Block Symposium, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 48)
    - Twentieth International Conference on the Physics of Electronic and Atomic Collisions, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 49)
    - "Casimir Effects -- Answers and Questions" talk presented at Max-Planck-Institut für Kernphysik, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 50)
    - Aspen Center for Physics, 1997-1998 (Box 26, Folder 51)
    - Alexander von Humboldt Association of America annual meeting, 1997-2001 (Box 26, Folder 52)
    - Institute for Theoretical Atomic Molecular and Optical Physics (ITAMP) Topical Group Workshop on Casimir Forces, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 53)
    - "Notes on Casimir Effects" transparencies for presentations at ITAMP, Harvard, and Los Alamos, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 54)
    - Physics and Theoretical Division Colloquium, Los Alamos National Laboratory, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 55)
    - Symmetry Found and Lost Conference, Institute for Advanced Study, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 56)
    - Aspen Center for Physics, 1999-2001 (Box 26, Folder 57)
    - CUSPEA and Beyond symposium, 2001 (Box 26, Folder 58)
    - Symposium to Honor Professor Henry Stroke, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 59)
    - Institute for Advanced Study conference, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 60)
    - Gordon Conference, undated (Box 26, Folder 61)
    - Presentation notes on "The H+ + CH4 -> H2+ + CH3 process in the double scattering model," by Shakeshaft and Spruch, undated (Box 26, Folder 62)
    - Sigma Pi Sigma Colloquium, undated (Box 26, Folder 63)
    - Conference on High Rydberg States, undated (Box 26, Folder 64)
    - Rolls of conference participants, undated (Box 26, Folder 65)
    - Transparencies on vacuum fluctuations, undated (Box 26, Folder 66)
    - Ninth International Conference on Photonic, Electronic, and Atomic Collisions talk on variational principles and variational bounds, undated (Box 26, Folder 67)
    - Notes from University of Colorado Summer Institute, undated (Box 26, Folder 68)
    - Transparencies used in talk at John Blair Symposium, undated (Box 26, Folder 69)
  - Subseries D: Awards and Honors, 1967-2001; 1984-2001
    - Brooklyn College Alumni Award of Honor, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Alexander von Humboldt Award, 1984-1988 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Alexander von Humboldt Award, 1988-1997 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Alexander von Humboldt Award, 1988, 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Golden Dozen Award, 1990 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Davisson-Germer Prize, 1991-1992 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Printed text of NYU Physics website in honor of Larry Spruch, 2001 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Articles by Larry Spruch for NYU Physics website, 2001 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Babb, James F., "Casimir-Polder effects in Rydberg atoms" (for NYU Physics website), undated (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Hahn, Yukap, "Variational bounds on scattering parameters" (for NYU Physics website), undated (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Lieb, Elliot H., "A Brief Review of Thomas-Fermi Theory" (for NYU Physics website), 2000 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Lieber, Michael, "Larry Spruch and the three-body problem" (for NYU Physics website), undated (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Rau, A. R. P., "Larry Spruch and Variational Principles" (for NYU Physics website), undated (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Rosenberg, Leonard, "Modified Effective Range Theory" (for NYU Physics website), undated (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Schaden, Martin, "Lamb and Casimir Energies and Periodic Classical Rays" (for NYU Physics website), 2000 (Box 41, Folder 8)
- Series V: Research, 1949-2004